https://oiglobalpartners.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
OI Global Partners takes your privacy seriously. We will never sell, rent or disclose your personal information to any third party without your consent. Unless you give OI Global Partners explicitly permission to act otherwise, the following privacy policy will guide the way we treat the personal information you provide to us.
The data we collect and why we collect it
We will not collect personal data from you unless you provided it voluntarily. So if you would rather not give us your telephone number, for example, please do not submit it. However, if you require a response to your query we will need some way of making contact. You need only supply one contact method if you wish, but the more details you provide the easier it is for us to respond.
Other OI Global Partners sites
OI Global Partners offers other online tools and services through websites that have their own privacy policies and users should be aware and check those privacy policies before use.
Cookies
We do use cookies on our website (https://oiglobalpartners.com). If you would like to know more about cookies and how to control or delete them, you can learn more on http://www.aboutcookies.org.
Google Analytics
We use Google Analytics to understand how our website is being used. This data helps us to improve the user experience on the site. You can read more about Google’s approach to data on: http://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html.
How to contact us
If you have any questions about this privacy policy please contact us.
© 2020 OI Global Partners.
